urindianconsumer.in 2019-07-23

# Privacy policy – Ur IndianConsumer

### General information

All users with their consent have clicked on the ‘I accept’ popup which is seen up front when you visit this website for the first time.By doing so they abide by our following terms,conditions and policies.

One of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by Ur IndianConsumer and how we use it.When you create an account and profile on the Ur IndianConsumer Platform, we collect your name, contact information (including your telephone number), and other information you provide, such as topics that you know about or find interesting. Your name, photo, and any other information that you choose to add to your public-facing profile will be available for viewing to users of the Ur IndianConsumer Platform. Once you create a profile, other users will be able to see in your profile certain information about your activity on the Ur IndianConsumer Platform, such as the questions and answers you post, your followers and who you follow, topics of interest to you, the information you list as credentials, and your edits to Your Content. If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us through email.

### Log files

Ur IndianConsumer follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites.

We do not sell your personal data– such as your name and contact information – to third parties to use for their own marketing purposes.

Ur IndianConsumer uses the information we collect for the following purposes:

  * Provide our Services.
  * Analytics. To gather metrics to better understand how users access and use the Ur IndianConsumer Platform; to evaluate and improve the Ur IndianConsumer Platform, including the Ad Services and personalization, and to develop new products and services.
  * Comply with Law. To comply with legal obligations, as part of our general business operations, and for other business administration purposes.
  * Prevent Misuse. Where we believe necessary to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person or violations of our Terms of Service or this Privacy Policy.

### Privacy policies

You may consult this list to find the Privacy Policy for each of the user,advertising partners of Incubator.

Your contact information will be used to communicate with you (via e-mail, phone, text message, through the Ur IndianConsumer Platform or otherwise). When you communicate with us (via email, phone, text message, through the Ur IndianConsumer Platform or otherwise), we may maintain a record of your communication. By disclosing your contact information to Ur IndianConsumer, you consent to our use of your contact information to communicate with you.

Third-party ad servers or ad networks uses technologies like cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons that are used in their respective advertisements and links that appear on Incubator, which are sent directly to users’ browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These technologies are used to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on websites that you visit.

Note that Ur IndianConsumer has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

### Third party policies

Incubator’s Privacy Policy does not apply to other advertisers or websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy Policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information. It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of certain options. You may find a complete list of these Privacy Policies and their links here: Privacy Policy Links.

You can choose to disable cookies through your individual browser options. To know more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers, it can be found at the browsers’ respective websites. What Are Cookies?

### Children Information

Another part of our priority is adding protection for children while using the internet. We encourage parents and guardians to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity.

Incubator does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. If you think that your child provided this kind of information on our website, we encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.

### Online privacy

This privacy policy applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regards to the information that they shared and/or collect in Ur IndianConsumer. This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.  
By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its Terms and Conditions.

### Spam and Misuse

If we find users spamming our website with multiple posts over and over again in order to gain more khushi points then such an activity will be dealt with utmost strictness.We completely keep the right to delete such spams and users comments,posts and accounts.Our platform is designed to help people and so we will be taking strict actions for maintaining its sanity.

### Plagiarism

We do not take responsibility of any content which our users have copied form any other user or platform.We are just a forum platform and we urge every user to make good use of it for the betterment of people.If any user is seen to post content which is owned by some other rightful owner we would like you to report the post/content and we shall immediately delete it from our platform.For more information you can contact us at contact@urindianconsumer.in .

 _ **Disclaimer**_

 _The views and opinions mentioned in the media or comments in past or present on our website are those of the authors or speakers and do not necessarily represent or reflect the views and opinions of everyone viewing it. The sole purpose of the content is for knowledge and awareness of viewers/consumers.Copyright Disclaimer, Under the Indian Copyright Act 1957,allowance is made for ‘fair use’ for purposes such as criticism,comment, news reporting, teaching, scholarship, and research.Fair use is a use permitted by copyright statute that might otherwise be infringing. Non-profit, educational or personal use tips the balance in favor of fair use.If you have a complaint about something or find our content   to be inappropriate, Any infringement if found was not done on purpose._
